<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><toc xmlns="http://www.oxygenxml.com/ns/webhelp/toc" xmlns:xhtml="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><title><span xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" class="title">Visiting Student's AirClassroom Guide to Shanks 360 </span></title><topic href="c-introduction-student.html" data-id="c-introduction-student.dita"><title>Welcome to Shanks 360!</title><shortdesc><p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" class="shortdesc">In this room you'll find everything you need to conduct a productive and creative workshop, lecture, or conference. Navigating a college campus for the first time can be tough, but we're here to help! </p>
</shortdesc><topicmeta></topicmeta></topic><topic href="c-price.html" data-id="c-price.dita"><title>AirClassroom Prices for Shanks 360</title><shortdesc><p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" class="shortdesc">We strive to give you the fairest price for our space. Our prices are non-negotiable, but we have taken every measure to make sure that they are the fairest deal you'll get.</p>
</shortdesc><topicmeta></topicmeta></topic><topic href="t-parking.html" data-id="t-parking.dita"><title>Where to park nearest Shanks Hall</title><shortdesc><p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" class="shortdesc">There is ample parking all over the Virginia Tech campus, but below are the best spots to ensure a clear and easy walk to Shanks Hall.</p>
</shortdesc><topicmeta></topicmeta></topic><topic href="c-food-suggestion.html" data-id="c-food-suggestion.dita"><title>Where to eat near Shanks Hall</title><shortdesc><p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" class="shortdesc">If you would like to cater for your event in Shanks or grab a bite to eat during a break, there is no shortage of great restuarants nearby.</p>
</shortdesc><topicmeta></topicmeta></topic><topic href="c-room-rules.html" data-id="c-room-rules.dita"><title>Shanks 360 Room Rules</title><shortdesc><p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" class="shortdesc">When you signed your lease for AirClassroom, you were given a list of rules for this room and you signed saying you would abide by them. For your conveneince we have attached the list here so you are able to reference it. We hope this ensures a comfortable and clean stay for you.</p>
</shortdesc><topicmeta></topicmeta></topic><topic href="t-room-rearrange.html" data-id="t-room-rearrange"><title>How to Rearrange the Classroom</title><shortdesc><p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" class="shortdesc">The room can be rearranged to better suit your needs if you prefer a meeting style to the lecture/workshop set up.</p>
</shortdesc><topicmeta></topicmeta></topic><topic href="t-projector.html" data-id="t-projector"><title>How to use the projector </title><shortdesc><p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" class="shortdesc">The projector is connected to the Mac desktop computer that is nearest the white board.</p>
</shortdesc><topicmeta></topicmeta></topic><topic href="t-internet.html" data-id="t-internet.dita"><title>How to use the Internet </title><shortdesc><p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" class="shortdesc">Complementary WiFi is something we are very proud to offer for our guests, in order to access the WiFi, first set up a profile on the DuoMobile application so that you can do Two-Facter Authentication. See the Two-Factor Authentication Tab if you are unsure of how to do this.  </p>
</shortdesc><topicmeta></topicmeta><topic href="t-two-factor.html" data-id="t-two-factor.dita"><title>How to Use Two-Factor Authentication</title><shortdesc><p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" class="shortdesc">Two-Factor Authentication is our way of making sure that your personal content is protected. We believe it is our first priority to make sure your property is safe.</p>
</shortdesc><topicmeta></topicmeta></topic></topic><topic href="t-computer.html" data-id="t-computer.dita"><title>How to use the Mac Desktop Computer</title><shortdesc><p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" class="shortdesc">The Mac Desktops are top of the line computers that are up to date with the latest Apple technology.  </p>
</shortdesc><topicmeta></topicmeta><topic href="c-computer-programs.html" data-id="c-computer-programs.dita"><title>Adobe Software on Mac Desktops</title><shortdesc><p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" class="shortdesc">The Mac Desktops have several up-to-date Adobe Creative Cloud Software orograms installed for your convenience. You can login to the Creative Cloud using the same login username and password that you did to get into the computer.  </p>
</shortdesc><topicmeta></topicmeta><topic href="t-adobe-programs.html" data-id="adobe-programs.dita"><title>How to Save Files from the Adobe Creative Cloud</title><shortdesc><p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" class="shortdesc">The Adobe Creative Cloud has a lot of excellent software available to use. If you are unsure of how to use a program, be sure to visit the Adobe Creative Cloud website for their helpful tutorials. </p>
</shortdesc><topicmeta></topicmeta></topic></topic></topic><topic href="t-cleaning.html" data-id="t-cleaning.dita"><title>How to Clean Up Shanks 360</title><shortdesc><p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" class="shortdesc">We are committed to keeping our spaces clean for our guests. Pay it forward and make sure that you are leaving the room as clean as you found it.</p>
</shortdesc><topicmeta></topicmeta></topic><topic href="c-works-cited.html" data-id="concept_dk5_y4c_1y"><title>Works Cited</title><shortdesc><p xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml" class="shortdesc">Below you'll find reference links for each of the pictures used on this site.</p>
</shortdesc><topicmeta></topicmeta></topic></toc>